A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.2, Series 300 Latin America - Series 833 Lebanon FA387b
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Jamaica, 1950-1976; 437; 6 box(es); 6 __Boxes
  - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, 437.A
    - University College of the West Indies - Turk, David Charles, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - University College of the West Indies - Went, Lodewyk Nicolaas, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - University College of the West Indies - Weston, Peter Alexander, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - University College of the West Indies - Cruickshank, Robert, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - University College of the West Indies - Exchange Program, 1964-1967 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Jamaica - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 437.D
    - Institute of Jamaica - Botany, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - University College of the West Indies - Hoyte, David A.N., 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - University College of the West Indies - Marine Biology, 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - University College of the West Indies - Plant Biochemistry, 1952-1956 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - University College of the West Indies - Zoology, 1952-1956 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - University of the West Indies - Food Crops, 1967-1971 (Box 4, Folder 49-51)
    - University of the West Indies - Sweet Potato Study, 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - University of the West Indies - Williams, Holman Eugene, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Jamaica - Humanities and Arts, 437.R
    - University College of the West Indies - Archival Program, 1957-1963, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 54-56)
    - University College of the West Indies - Arts Festival, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - University College of the West Indies - Folk Music, 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - University College of the West Indies - Creole Dialects, 1958-1961 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - University College of the West Indies - Creole English, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - University College of the West Indies - Creole Linguistics, 1961-1963, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - University College of the West Indies - Vaz, Noel, 1960-1962 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Jamaica - Social Sciences, 437.S
    - Foreign Affairs (Ministry of) - Books, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - University College of the West Indies - Economics, 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - University College of the West Indies - Caribbean and Latin American Conference, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - University College of the West Indies - International Relations, 1962 January-1964 August (Box 5, Folder 66-67)
    - University of the West Indies - International Relations, 1964 September-1971 April (Box 6, Folder 68-73)
  - Jamaica - Virus Studies, 437.V
    - University College of the West Indies - Jones, Keith, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - University of the West Indies - Griffiths, Bertie Bernard, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 75)
  - Jamaica - Schistosomiasis, 437.W
    - University of the West Indies - Dalton, Peter, 1969-1972, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 76)
- Trinidad and Tobago, 1955-1975; 451; 3 box(es)
  Six subseries as follows: 451 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 451 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 451 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 451 R Humanities and arts 451 S Social Sciences 451 V Virus study
  - Trinidad and Tobago - General (No Program), 451.GEN
    - Moosai-Maharaj, Stephan, July-December 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - St. Andrew's School, August-October, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Medical Sciences, 451.A
    - Health - Charles, R.M.F., 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Trinidad General Hospital - Bacteriology, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Sherlock, Philip M., 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 451.D
    - University College of the West Indies - Agriculture, 1960 September-1965 September (Box 1, Folder 6-11)
    - University College of the West Indies - Agriculture, 1965 October-1968 August, 1972 January (Box 2, Folder 12-15)
    - University of the West Indies - Ahmed, Nazeer, January-June 1967 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - University of the West Indies - Haynes, P.H., February-March 1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - University of the West Indies - Henderson, Thomas Horatio, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - University of the West Indies - Nematodes Symposium, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - University of the West Indies - Osbourn, Denns Frederick, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - University of the West Indies - Soil Science, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - University of the West Indies - Tai, Egbert A., December 1966-October 1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - University of the West Indies - Tropical Root Crops Symposium, April 1966-October 1968 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - University of the West Indies - Visits, June 1968-March 1969 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - University of the West Indies - Wilson, Peter N., 1960-1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Humanities and Arts, 451.R
    - Education - Archives, 1957-1958 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Little Carib Theatre - Henry, Jeff, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Little Carib Theatre - John, Errol, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Little Carib Theatre - Laird, Colin, June-September 1961 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Little Carib Theatre - Machiz, Herbert, 1961-1962 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Walcott, Derek Alton, 1966-1971 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Walcott, Derek Alton, 1966-1971 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Social Sciences, 451.S
    - External Affairs - Books, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Trinidad and Tobago - Virus Studies, 451.V
    - Administration, August 1975 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Green, Arthur Edwin, 1953-1954, 1956-1958 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Spence, Leslie P., 1961-1963, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Tikasingh, Elisha S., 1963-1967 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Windward Islands, 1965-1972; 455; 2 box(es)
  Three subseries as follows: 455 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 455 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 455 W Schistosomiasis
  - Windward Islands - General (No Program), 455.GEN
    - Education, Health and Social Affairs - Pilgrim, Vance, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Windward Islands - Medical Sciences, 455.A
    - Health - Lees, Ronald E.M., January-April 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Planned Parenthood Association, 1967-1969, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Windward Islands - Schistosomiasis, 455.W
    - Economic Survey, 1965 December-1972 November (Box 1, Folder 4-7)
    - Economic Survey - Supplementary Material, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - Economic Survey - Supplementary Material, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10-15)
- South Asia Region, 1915-1970; 460; 1 box(es)
  Two subseries as follows: 460 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 460 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture)
  - South Asia Region - General (No Program), 460.GEN
    - Program and Policy, 1915-1916, 1921, 1932, 1934, 1936, 1943,1947-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Program and Policy - Report Folder - Pro-1, Pro-2, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Program and Policy - Report Folder - Pro-3, Pro-4, Pro-5, Pro-6, 1953, 1956, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Wray, Joe D. - Diary, January-February 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - South Asia Region - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 460.D
    - Sikkam - Agriculture - Narasimham, K.L., 1960-1964 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Sri Lanka, 1949-1969; 462; 4 box(es)
  Five subseries as follows: 462 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 462 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 462 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 462 R Humanities and arts 462 S Social sciences
  - Sri Lanka - General (No Program), 462.GEN
    - Health - Kahawita, Don Lionel Joannes, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Health - Wijewardene, Vimala, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Human Ecology, 1949-1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - University of Ceylon - Baptist, Noel Garth, 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - University of Ceylon - Social Medicine, 1950-1952 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - University of Ceylon - Village Studies, 1950-1952, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Sri Lanka - Medical Sciences, 462.A
    - Health - Karunaratne, Wickremarachige Ajitha, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - University of Ceylon, 1953, 1956-1963 (Box 1, Folder 8-9)
    - University of Ceylon - Abhayaratne, Osmond E.R., 1954, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - University of Ceylon - Anatomy - Chanmugam, Paul K., 1952-1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - University of Ceylon - Attygalle, Nicholas, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - University of Ceylon - Cabraal, Shelton A., 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - University of Ceylon - de Silva Percival C.C., 1954-1955 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Ceylon - Waas, Moderage, Joseph, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - University of Ceylon - Watson, Richard S.S., 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Sri Lanka - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 462.D
    - Agriculture - Chemistry, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Agriculture - Fernando, Henry E., 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Soil Chemistry - Ponnamperuma, Felix Nelson, 1955-1956, 1959-1960, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - University of Ceylon - Seneviratna, K.A.D. Peter S., 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - University of Ceylon - Wikramanayake, V.E.A., 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sri Lanka - Humanities and Arts, 462.R
    - Galappatty, Gunasena A., 1958-1961 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Tilakasiri, J., 1959-1961, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - University of Ceylon - American Studies, 1957-1961 (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - University of Ceylon - de Souza, A.T.A., 1959-1960 (Box 2, Folder 25-26)
    - University of Ceylon - Drama, 1955-1957 (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - University of Ceylon - Educational Research - Green, T.L., 1951-1955 (Box 3, Folder 28-29)
    - University of Ceylon - Linguistics, 1958 October-1966 May (Box 3, Folder 30-33)
    - University of Ceylon - Linguistics - Coimbatore Summer School, 1958-1959 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - University of Ceylon - Linguistics - Hettiaratchi, D.E., 1951-1960, 1963, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - University of Ceylon - Linguistics - Sledd, James H., November 1958-December 1960 (Box 4, Folder 36-37)
    - University of Ceylon - Malalasekera, G.P., James H., 1952-1955 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - University of Ceylon - Sarathchandra, E.R., 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - University of Ceylon - Somadasa, K.D., 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Welikala, D.P., 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Sri Lanka - Social Sciences, 462.S
    - Defense and External Affairs (Ministry of) - Books, 1958-1960, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Defense and External Affairs (Ministry of) - Training Abroad, 1958-1959, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - University of Ceylon - Wikkramatileke, Rudolph (Mr. and Mrs.), 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Hong Kong, 1949-1969; 463; 2 box(es)
  Four subseries as follows: 463 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 463 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 463 R Humanities and arts 463 S Social sciences
  - Hong Kong - General (No Program), 463.GEN
    - Chinese University, 1963-1965, 1967-1969 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Chinese University - Supplementary Material, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Hong Kong - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 463.D
    - University of Hong Kong - Stenton, Harry, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hong Kong - Humanities and Arts, 463.R
    - New Asia College - Humanities, September 1958-October 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6-9)
    - Scott, A.C., 1957-1958 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - University of Hong Kong - Green, A.T.W., 1960-1961 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - University of Hong Kong - Ng, Tung-King, 1958-1959 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hong Kong - Social Sciences, 463.S
    - Chinese University - Geography - Chen, Cheng-siang, 1965-1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - University of Hong Kong - Housing, 1954-1957 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - University of Hong Kong - Kirby, E. Stuart, 1949-1955 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- India, 1948-1986; 464; 95 box(es); 95 __Boxes
  Ten subseries as follows: 464 (no program letter; general material which does not fit into a particular program area) 464 A Medical sciences (research conducted in medical schools or medical research institutes, research directly applicable to the mental and physical health of human beings) 464 C Nursing (nursing education, public health nursing) 464 D Natural sciences and agriculture (research usually conducted in departments outside of medical schools, research in pure science, veterinary medicine or agriculture) 464 E Fellowships, scholarships, training awards 464 I Malaria 464 K Health services (epidemiology, reform, public health administration, laboratories, vital statistics, and particularly sanitary engineering) 464 R Humanities and arts 464 S Social sciences 464 V Virus studies
  - Agriculture, 1953-June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, 1953-June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, 1953-June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, 1953-June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture, 1953-June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture, 1953-June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agriculture, 1953-June 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agriculture, July 1958-December 1961 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Agriculture, July 1958-December 1961 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Agriculture, July 1958-December 1961 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Agriculture, July 1958-December 1961 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Agriculture, July 1958-December 1961 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Agriculture, July 1958-December 1961 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Agriculture, January 1962-December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Agriculture, January 1962-December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Agriculture, January 1962-December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Agriculture, January 1962-December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Agriculture, January 1962-December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Agriculture, January 1962-December 1964 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Agriculture, January 1965-August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Agriculture, January 1965-August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Agriculture, January 1965-August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Agriculture, January 1965-August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Agriculture, January 1965-August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Agriculture, January 1965-August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Agriculture, January 1965-August 1968 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Agriculture, September 1968-December 1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Agriculture, September 1968-December 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Agriculture, September 1968-December 1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Agriculture, September 1968-December 1971 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Agriculture - Administration, May 1956-July 1957 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Agriculture - Administration, May 1956-July 1957 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Agriculture - Administration, May 1956-July 1957 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Agriculture - Administration, August 1957-October 1958 (Box 6, Folder 41)
  - Agriculture - Administration, November 1958-March 1960 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Agriculture - Administration, November 1958-March 1960 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Agriculture - Administration, November 1958-March 1960 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Agriculture - Administration, November 1958-March 1960 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Agriculture - Administration, November 1958-March 1960 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Agriculture - Administration, November 1958-March 1960 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Agriculture - Administration, November 1958-March 1960 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Agriculture - Administration, April 1960-December 1961 (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1962-December 1962 (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 68)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 69)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 70)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 71)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 72)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 74)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1963-January 1964 (Box 10, Folder 75)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 76)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 77)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 78)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 79)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 80)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 81)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 82)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 83)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 84)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1964-February 1965 (Box 11, Folder 85)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 86)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 87)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 88)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 89)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 90)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 91)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 92)
  - Agriculture - Administration, March 1965-January 1966 (Box 12, Folder 93)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Agriculture - Administration, February 1966-December 1966 (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Agriculture - Administration, January 1967-September 1967 (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 112)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 113)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 114)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 115)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 116)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 117)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 118)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 119)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 120)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 121)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 122)
  - Agriculture - Administration, October 1967-May 1969 (Box 15, Folder 123)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 124)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 125)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 126)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 127)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 128)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 129)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 130)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 131)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 132)
  - Agriculture - Administration, June 1969-December 1971 (Box 16, Folder 133)
  - AGR-15 Agriculture Byrnes, F.C. Report on Trip to India, Sept. 20 - Oct. 10, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 134)